There are humanoid species,
such as humans, elves, and dwarves,
who are blessed by the gods of light.
Then there are demons,
which, while few in number,
are blessed by darkness and individually
far stronger than humanoids.
These two forces have clashed for millennia,
dividing the vast continent of Leunders
into the east and west.
However, when a moderate demon king
took the throne three hundred years ago,
the situation stabilized, and humanoids
grew accustomed to a temporary peace.
In the fifth month of the year 2826,
that peace was broken,
and under a new demon king,
the demons launched an all-out attack
against the humanoids that would
be known as the Great Invasion.
With no regard for their own casualties,
the demons fought fiercely,
and several humanoid nations
fell the blink of an eye.
By the fourth month
of the following year, 2827,
the Gargan Empire, which boasted the largest
humanoid fighting force, was destroyed.
With nowhere left to turn,
humanoids took desperate measures.
They gathered their remaining troops
and engaged the main
demon army in a reckless battle
while a suicide squad entered the demon king's
castle, functionally the enemy base,
to assassinate the demon king
in a final act of desperation.
Are you all right?
Theron!
Go on without me.
I'll handle these guys.
We're counting on you.
Damn... What a pain in the ass.
Let's go.
What is that?
Above you!
Urza!
What was that attack?
That was Elimination, an unblockable
high-level spell that destroys everything.
I need to do something drastic.
My only option is to release
the gemstone's magic power.
If my wielder is risking his life,
then I have no choice but to join you.
I'm sorry.
Laws of wisdom, become a flash of light
to destroy the ignorance of darkness!
It's finally over.
Hey.
You can't respond to me anymore, can you?
It's quiet.
I guess I'm the only survivor.
Everything I wanted to protect is gone now.
My home, my family, my friends, my beloved...
I've lost them all.
Now, at last, I too can...
A magical item?
If that thing's magic power
goes out of control...
Is this... my room?
No, that's impossible.
I must be dreaming.
Kyle, how long are you going to sleep?
Get up already.
Oh, you're already awake.
Liese...
Hey.
What's wrong? Does your stomach hurt?
Huh?
I get it now. This is a dream.
W-Wait a minute...
I don't care if it is.
I'm so glad to see you again, Liese.
What's gotten into you?
What are you thinking?!
I don't know what that was, but I need
time to emotionally prepare myself!
You jerk!
Huh?
I can feel pain.
Maybe it's not a dream?
Yeah, it's not a dream.
I'm younger, aren't I?
Moreover, I thought I suffered
near-fatal injuries.
If this isn't a dream, what's going on?
The town is back to normal.
Liese is alive and well, and I'm young again.
I can only assume I've returned to the past.
But that's not possible.
Does that mean this thing was the cause?
There's no way a spell to return to the past—
Whatever the case,
I guess I still get hungry.
Liese must've made this for me.
She frequently came over to cook,
since my mom and I couldn't.
That's good!
I haven't had a proper meal in so long.
I ate way too much.
Hey. I'm starving.
What? Hang on!
You've gotta be kidding me!
You ate it all yourself?!
Theron...
Damn it!
I was looking forward to this, since
Liese got all fancy with the recipe.
Theron...
You could've at least left me a bite.
We were fighting together
until just moments ago, but...
You seriously ate all of it.
What are you looking at?
I, uh...
What day of what month and year is it today?
What're you on about?
It's the 24th day of the fifth
month of the year 2823.
Really? You're sure?
Yeah, it's definitely the 24th day
of the fifth month of the year 2823.
Oh, right. Today's your birthday, yeah?
Then I guess it's fine.
We'll say that meal was your birthday present.
Kinda cheap, don't you think?
Besides, that wasn't yours to give.
Man, I'm starving.
I'm gonna go get something from Liese.
If I kiss the ground and beg,
she'll probably feed me a full meal.
As usual, he'll do anything
to achieve his goals.
Now then, what should I do?
If I really have magically
returned to the past...
Well... I'll have to ask her about it.
Oh, Kyle. Rare to see you here.
It's morning, Mom.
Were you up all night reading again?
Morning already?
I can never tell what time it is in here.
To be honest, I have a magic question for you.
Gosh, I don't know if I'll have an answer.
You're an archmage.
One of only a handful in the country.
Not many people know more
about magic than you do.
I suppose not.
Listen, are there any spells
to return you to the past?
There are.
What? Really?
They're not very well known, but there
are definitely spells that affect time.
But we merely know they exist.
Nobody can use them.
It's a matter of the required magic power.
Magic power?
Even if the greatest mage in history
used all their magic power,
I doubt they could travel back
even a single second.
Then what about with
the help of a magic item?
I see. An interesting idea.
You mean using a magic item
as a catalyst to store magic power?
Even then, it would take someone over
a millennium to store that much magic power.
What if you used the Forbidden Rite?
The Forbidden Rite...
A sacrificial ritual to turn
life force into magic power.
Where did you learn about that?
I just saw it in a book.
I don't know much about it.
I see.
Even with the Forbidden Rite,
it'd be impossible.
You'd need the lives of half
the humanoids on the continent.
In other words, it is possible
if you sacrifice half the land.
On top of that,
there's no catalyst capable of storing the
magic power it'd take to go back in time.
But if one... did exist...
I think it'd be in this book.
Ah, here we are.
The legendary Divine Dragon's Heart
is just about your only option.
The ancient magic kingdom of Xarles
prospered for a thousand years
thanks to the Divine Dragon's Heart
and the tremendous magic power it contained.
But its power was eventually depleted,
leading to the kingdom's downfall.
I'd bet the Divine Dragon's Heart could store
enough magic power to return to the past.
But it's been missing
for over a thousand years.
Perhaps it's already fallen into demon hands.
I see.
This is nice.
Huh?
It's been ages since we last talked this much.
You quit your sword training
and you've been avoiding me lately...
Not on purpose!
I, uh... I'm sorry.
I swear! I've really missed you!
But today, you seem more mature than usual.
It's like you're here from the future.
What?
Just kidding.
Gosh, I'm so hungry.
Liese cooked for us again today, right?
Oh, uh... I ate it all.
What?
Sorry! I couldn't help myself.
It's fine.
Oh, that reminds me!
Today's your birthday, isn't it?
How like you to forget
your own son's birthday.
Then that meal can be your birthday present.
Why is everyone trying
to cheap out on my gift?
Returning to the past, huh?
What did he want to do over?
There you are.
Sorry about this morning!
At least you feel bad about it.
I only did it because I had
a weird dream that upset me.
I'm really sorry!
What kind of dream?
Was it one about me dying?
Yeah, something like that.
So that's why you were so distraught.
Huh. I see.
In that case, I forgive you.
Besides, today's your birthday.
Happy birthday, Kyle!
Our town is close to demon territory.
It was the first to be attacked
in the Great Invasion.
They burned it to the ground,
leaving it a hellscape.
That's how I lost Liese.
On that day, I swore I'd avenge her.
Kyle. Kyle?
What's wrong, Kyle?
You're scaring me.
It's nothing.
Really? Then I guess it's fine.
Three years from now, this peace will end.
I'm the only one who knows.
If I do nothing, I'll be forced
to witness the same thing over again.
I'll lose them again—
My family, my home, my world,
and the people I love.
I'll change it.
My fate—
I'm going to change my fate!
I'll change my stupid fate
and the fate of the whole world!
I swear I will!
No matter what it takes!
This is my advantage.
I've logged all the future events I
can remember in this notebook, but...
Still...
What should I be doing?
I came here from four years in the future.
The demons will launch an all-out
attack three years from now,
but even if I tell people to prepare,
nobody will believe me.
I'll have to kill the mysterious
demon king myself!
That's not happening.
Even if luck goes completely in my favor,
I can't do this alone at my current strength.
No...
I should check first.
Next Time
The Hero's Conditions
Next time: "The Hero's Conditions."